#### Contact

margaret.l.whitehead@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/margaretwhitehead-msn-rn-ccrn-cvrna5682013 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Heart Failure LVADs

Heart Transplant

## Languages

Spanish

#### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN)

Cardiovascular Registered Nurse (CVRN-BC)

Registered Nurse

#### Honors-Awards

Outstanding Graduate Student Nurse Hero Award

# Margaret Whitehead, MSN, RN, CCRN, CVRN

Circulatory Support Services Supervisor at CHI St. Luke's Health Houston, Texas Area

## Summary

Highly organized, adaptable, motivated, and experienced Registered Nurse with a history of working with high acuity patients through the continuum of care: from fast-paced, critical settings to the outpatient clinic. Exceeds in delivering results during critical moments. Dedicated to providing quality patient care through compassion, collaboration, patient education, and excellence.

## Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health

4 years

Circulatory Support Services Supervisor January 2020 - Present (5 months)

**LVAD Coordinator** 

June 2016 - December 2019 (3 years 7 months)

Baylor College of Medicine Research Nurse December 2015 - June 2016 (7 months)

**ECMO** Research

Memorial Hermann Health System
Registered Nurse
June 2012 - December 2015 (3 years 7 months)
Houston, Texas Area

Heart Transplant ICU
Center for Advanced Heart Failure
Heart and Vascular Institute

Harris Health System Registered Nurse January 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 7 months)
Inpatient Psychiatry Unit
Ben Taub General Hospital

# Education

Texas Woman's University

Masters of Science in Nursing, Health Systems Management, Business

Administration · (2012 - 2016)

University of Houston-Victoria
Bachelors of Science, Nursing · (2010 - 2010)

Texas Tech University

Bachelors of Art, Psychology, Nutritional Sciences · (2004 - 2008)